Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Information File, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 78, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Remarks by Herman Edelsberg, 1966; Publication (Box 78, Folder 6)
    Author: Herman Edelsberg
  - Item 17: Statement for Joint Legislative Committee on Industrial and Labor Conditions, 1966; Publication (Box 78, Folder 6)
    Author: Jay Kramer
    Notes: November 29, 1966
  - Item 18: Excerpts, 1966; Publication (Box 78, Folder 6)
    Author: L. I. Brezhnev
    Notes: October 25, 1966
  - Item 19: Automation, People, and Pensions, 1966; Publication (Box 78, Folder 6)
    Notes: April 30, 1966
  - Item 20: Automation and the Changing Cities, 1966; Publication (Box 78, Folder 6)
    Author: Sam Zagoria
    Notes: May 19, 1966
  - Item 21: The Impact of Automation on Collective Bargaining, 1966; Publication (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Item 22: Collective Bargaining: How to Take the Frustration Out of Cybernation, 1966; Publication (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Item 23: The National Labor Relations Act: An Exercise in Industrial Democracy, 1966; Publication (Box 78, Folder 6)
    Author: Arnold Ordman
    Notes: June 9, 1966
  - Item 24: Ethics in Automation, 1966; Publication (Box 78, Folder 6)
    Notes: June 24, 1966
- Box: 78, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Agent Provocateur in the Labor Movement, Publication (Box 78, Folder 7)
    Author: Johannes Buchner
- Box: 78, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Staff Relations in the Civil Service, Publication (Box 78, Folder 8)
    Author: Great Britain Treasury
- Box: 78, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: State and Local Employees, Publication (Box 78, Folder 9)
- Box: 78, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Directory of State Merit Systems, 1962; Publication (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Fringe Benefits in State Government Employment, 1968; Publication (Box 78, Folder 10)
    Author: Council of State Governments
- Box: 78, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The State Technical Services Act of 1965, Publication (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Public Law 89-182, 1965; Publication (Box 78, Folder 11)
    Notes: September 14, 1965
- Box: 78, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Competitive Challenge to Steel, Publication (Box 78, Folder 12)
    Author: American Iron and Steel Institute
  - Item 2: The Competitive Challenge to Steel, 1963; Publication (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Blast Furnaces, Steelworks, Rolling Mills, 1967; Publication (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Blast Furnaces, Steel Works, and Rolling Mills, 1961; Publication (Box 78, Folder 12)
- Box: 78, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Steel in Era of Dramatic Growth, 1965; Publication (Box 78, Folder 13)
    Author: William J. Stephens
  - Item 2: Steel's Competitive Challenge, Publication (Box 78, Folder 13)
- Box: 78, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: It Could Happen Only in the U.S., 1956; Publication (Box 78, Folder 14)
    Author: Benjamin F. Fairless
- Box: 78, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Picture Story of Steel, Publication (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Steel Prices, the Steel Industry, and the National Economy, 1965; Publication (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: The Iron and Steel Trades, 1965; Publication (Box 78, Folder 15)
    Author: William Jacks & Company
  - Item 4: The Problems of Competition, 1965; Publication (Box 78, Folder 15)
    Author: Edgar B. Speer
  - Item 5: World Competition in Steel, 1963; Publication (Box 78, Folder 15)
    Author: John L. Young
  - Item 6: Steelmaking Flow Charts, Publication (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: The Near-Sighted Bellwether, Publication (Box 78, Folder 15)
    Author: David Cushman Coyle
  - Item 8: Steel Industry Steadily Growing, 1956; Publication (Box 78, Folder 15)
    Notes: May 1956
- Box: 78, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Comparison of Steel-Making Processes, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
- Box: 78, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Automation in the Iron and Steel Industry, Publication (Box 78, Folder 17)
- Box: 78, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Steel Workers and Technical Progress, 1959; Publication (Box 78, Folder 18)
    Notes: June 1959
- Box: 78, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Review of Iron and Steel Literature, 1960; Publication (Box 78, Folder 19)
    Author: Esther Chesire
    Notes: May-August 1960
- Box: 78, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Les Repercussions de L'Evolution Technique sur la Productivite, les Salaires, la Duree du Travail et L'Emploi, 1965; Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
    Notes: January 1, 1965
- Box: 78, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Why Nationalise Steel?, Publication (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: The Iron and Steel Bill, Publication (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Steel Nationalisation, 1965; Publication (Box 78, Folder 21)
    Author: Great Britain Ministry of Power
    Notes: April 1965
- Box: 78, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Steel: The Coming Redundancies and How to Fight Them, Publication (Box 78, Folder 22)
    Author: Dave Bailey
  - Item 2: Education and Training in the Iron and Steel Industry, Publication (Box 78, Folder 22)
    Author: Fanfare Press
- Box: 78, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Statistical Year Book, 1966; Publication (Box 78, Folder 23)
    Author: The Japan Iron & Steel Federation
- Box: 78, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Report to the President on Steel Prices, 1965; Publication (Box 78, Folder 24)
    Author: U.S. Council of Economic Advisers
  - Item 2: Basic Data Relating to Steel Prices, 1950; Publication (Box 78, Folder 24)
    Author: U.S. Joint Committee on the Economic Report
- Box: 78, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Economics and Technology, Publication (Box 78, Folder 25)
    Author: M. Gardner Clark
- Box: 78, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Principles of Accident Prevention, Publication (Box 78, Folder 26)
- Box: 78, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: The Steel Strike, 1959; Publication (Box 78, Folder 27)
    Notes: December 1959
  - Item 2: The Steel Strike, 1959; Publication (Box 78, Folder 27)
- Box: 78, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Steel: Problems of a Great Industry, 1937; Publication (Box 78, Folder 28)
    Author: Public Affairs Pamphlets
- Box: 78, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Wider Shareholding, Publication (Box 78, Folder 29)
    Author: Acton Society
  - Item 2: Investment Practices of Executives in Business and Industry, 1958; Publication (Box 78, Folder 29)
    Author: Nation's Business
  - Item 3: Restricted Stock Options, 1963; Publication (Box 78, Folder 29)
    Author: Industrial Relations Counselors
    Notes: March 1963
  - Item 4: Report on Employee Stock-Ownership Plans, Publication (Box 78, Folder 29)
- Box: 78, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 78, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Stone, Clay, and Glass Products, Publication (Box 78, Folder 30)
- Box: 78, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 78, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Industrial Disputes and the Canadian Act, 1917; Publication (Box 78, Folder 31)
    Author: Ben M. Selekman
    Notes: April 1917
- Box: 78, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 78, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Unofficial Strike, 1951; Publication (Box 78, Folder 32)
    Author: T.T. Paterson, F.J. Willett
  - Item 2: Strikes, Publication (Box 78, Folder 32)
  - Item 3: Aftermath of the Strikes, 1946; Publication (Box 78, Folder 32)
    Notes: April 1946
  - Item 4: The Trend of Strikes, 1963; Publication (Box 78, Folder 32)
    Author: H.A. Turner
  - Item 5: Strikes - and the Remedy, Publication (Box 78, Folder 32)
    Author: W.T. Colyer
- Box: 78, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 78, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Penalties for Striking, 1969; Publication (Box 78, Folder 33)
    Author: G.H. Sorrell, G.W. Ford
    Notes: August 1969
- Box: 78, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 78, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Fact Sheet on Work Stoppages in the Airline Industry, 1971; Publication (Box 78, Folder 34)
    Notes: April 9, 1971
- Box: 78, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 78, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Conflictos del Trabajo, 1968; Publication (Box 78, Folder 35)
    Author: Departamento Socio- Economico
- Box: 78, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 78, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: The General Motors Strike, 1945; Publication (Box 78, Folder 36)
    Notes: December 1945
- Box: 78, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 78, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: What Happened at Fords, Publication (Box 78, Folder 37)
    Author: Ken Weller, Ernie Stanton
- Box: 78, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 78, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Les Greves Generales au XX Siecle en Belgique, 1966; Publication (Box 78, Folder 38)
    Author: Leon Delsinne
  - Item 2: Les Greves "Contre la Loi Unique", 1961; Publication (Box 78, Folder 38)
    Author: Centre de Recherque et D'Information Socio-Politiques
    Notes: January 13, 1961
  - Item 3: Greve, Lock-Out et Conciliation Dans L'Avant-Projet Servais sur les Relations Collectives, 1963; Publication (Box 78, Folder 38)
    Notes: November 22, 1963
- Box: 78, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 78, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Enmore Enquiry Commission, 1948; Publication (Box 78, Folder 39)
    Author: British Guiana
    Notes: August 31, 1948
- Box: 79, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Industrial Courts Act 1919, 1967; Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Dispute Between FUE and Maintenance Craft Unions, Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
    Author: Con Murphy
- Box: 79, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Rand Formula, Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
    Author: Harold J. Clawson
- Box: 79, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Strikes and the Public, Publication (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Box: 79, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Stakingsrecht Voor Ambtenaren, 1966; Publication (Box 79, Folder 4)
    Author: Katholieke Bond van Overheidspersoneel
- Box: 79, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Strikes and Solutions, Publication (Box 79, Folder 5)
    Author: Eric Polisar
  - Item 2: Public Employees and the Right to Strike, 1967; Publication (Box 79, Folder 5)
    Notes: May 9, 1967
- Box: 79, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Coal Controversy, 1922; Publication (Box 79, Folder 6)
    Author: Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America
    Notes: May 1922
- Box: 79, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Statement of Facts and Summary, 1922; Publication (Box 79, Folder 7)
    Author: John F. Hylan
    Notes: December 1922
- Box: 79, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Mischief on the Building Sites, 1967; Publication (Box 79, Folder 8)
    Author: Industrial Research Information Services
    Notes: October 1967
- Box: 79, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Plant City Reactions to the Electrical Workers' Strike, 1946; Publication (Box 79, Folder 9)
    Notes: February 1946
- Box: 79, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Labor Disputes Statistics, 1964; Publication (Box 79, Folder 10)
- Box: 79, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Fact Sheet on Work Stoppages in the Farm Machinery and Equipment Industry, 1970; Publication (Box 79, Folder 11)
    Notes: June 15, 1970
- Box: 79, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Hachette une Experience Syndicale, 1970; Publication (Box 79, Folder 12)
    Author: Francois Maspero
- Box: 79, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Investigation of Strikes, Publication (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: What Happened at Woolf's, Publication (Box 79, Folder 13)
    Author: London Industrial Shop Stewards Defence Committee
- Box: 79, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Maiden Strike in India, Publication (Box 79, Folder 14)
    Author: Gopal Ghosh
- Box: 79, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Pacific Coast Longshoremen's Strike, 1934; Publication (Box 79, Folder 15)
    Author: National Longshoremen's Board
    Notes: September 25, 1934
- Box: 79, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Investigation, 1948; Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    Notes: December 20, 1948
- Box: 79, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: We Want 40, Publication (Box 79, Folder 17)
    Author: Jack Coward
- Box: 79, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Work Stoppages at Cape Kennedy, 1965; Publication (Box 79, Folder 18)
    Author: U.S. Missile Sites Labor Commission
- Box: 79, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Raadgevingen, Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Het Stakingsrecth, Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
    Author: Commissie Stakingsrecht
  - Item 3: Wettelijke Regeling van de Werkstaking, 1961; Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
    Author: Staatsdrukkerij
  - Item 4: Het Stakings Recht, Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
- Box: 79, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Work Stoppages, 1960; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
- Box: 79, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Effects of a Newspaper Strike on Retail Sales, 1966; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
    Author: Rikuma Ito
    Notes: July 1966
- Box: 79, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Strikes in the Plastics Industry, 1961; Publication (Box 79, Folder 22)
    Author: Jack N. Thornhill
- Box: 79, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Labor Troubles at Goldfield, NV, 1908; Publication (Box 79, Folder 23)
    Notes: February 3, 1908
- Box: 79, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Postal Staffs Face the Federal Government, Publication (Box 79, Folder 24)
    Author: John S. Baker
- Box: 79, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Railway Labor Dispute, 1971; Publication (Box 79, Folder 25)
    Notes: February 17, 1971
  - Item 2: The Commercial and Political Considerations Involved in the "Ann Arbor" Cases, 1893; Publication (Box 79, Folder 25)
    Author: Joseph Nimmo
- Box: 79, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Dispute at the Port Talbot Works of the British Steel Corporation, 1969; Publication (Box 79, Folder 26)
    Author: Great Britain Court of Inquiry
- Box: 79, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: A Studin of the Strike in Calcutta Tramways Company Limited, Publication (Box 79, Folder 27)
- Box: 79, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Adalshandelserna, 1931; Publication (Box 79, Folder 28)
    Author: Andra Upplagan
- Box: 79, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Der Sympathiestreik als Rechtswidriges Verhalten Gegenuber Dem Betroffenen Arbeitgeber, 1964; Publication (Box 79, Folder 29)
    Author: Heinz Reinermann
  - Item 2: Der Sympathiearbeitskampf, Publication (Box 79, Folder 29)
    Author: Marita Dohner
- Box: 79, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Work Stoppages Involving Teachers, 1963; Publication (Box 79, Folder 30)
- Box: 79, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: In Place of Strife, Publication (Box 79, Folder 31)
    Author: National Union of Teachers
  - Item 2: The Teachers' Strike, Publication (Box 79, Folder 31)
- Box: 79, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Bombay Textile General Strike, 1966; Publication (Box 79, Folder 32)
    Author: Communist Party
- Box: 79, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 79, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: So this is Free Speech!, 1935; Publication (Box 79, Folder 33)
    Author: American Civil Liberties Union
    Notes: January 1935
  - Item 2: State Regulation of the Right to Strike, Publication (Box 79, Folder 33)
    Author: Dewayne A. Stonebarger
  - Item 3: The Sit-Down as a Union Weapon, 1967; Publication (Box 79, Folder 33)
    Author: David I. Shair
  - Item 4: What About Strikes?, Publication (Box 79, Folder 33)
  - Item 5: The Strike: A Current Assessment, 1967; Publication (Box 79, Folder 33)
    Author: Benjamin Aaron
  - Item 6: Emergency Strikes, Publication (Box 79, Folder 33)
- Box: 79, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 79, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Union Committeemen and Wildcat Strikes, Publication (Box 79, Folder 34)
    Author: Correspondence
- Box: 79, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 79, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Employment of Full-Time Students at Special minimum Wages, 1971; Publication (Box 79, Folder 35)
    Author: United States Department of Labor
    Notes: November 1971
  - Item 2: Employment of Full-Time Students in Retail or Service Establishments at Special Minimum Wages, 1964; Publication (Box 79, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: Summer Employment of College Students in the Federal Government, 1963; Publication (Box 79, Folder 35)
    Notes: March 14, 1963
- Box: 79, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 79, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Student Financial Aid in Higher Education, Publication (Box 79, Folder 36)
- Box: 79, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 79, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Cross-Cultural Education, 1965; Publication (Box 79, Folder 37)
- Box: 79, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 79, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Studies of Student Personnel, Publication (Box 79, Folder 38)
    Author: Frances M. Wilson, Morris Krugman
- Box: 79, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 79, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: College Applicants Entrants Dropouts, Publication (Box 79, Folder 39)
- Box: 79, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 79, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Contracting Out, Publication (Box 79, Folder 40)
    Author: Margaret K. Chandler, Leonard R. Sayles
- Box: 79, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 79, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: The Duty to Bargain and a Look at Recent Subcontracting Cases, 1965; Publication (Box 79, Folder 41)
    Author: Machinery & Allied Products Institute
    Notes: December 16, 1965
  - Item 2: Collective Bargaining and Contracting Out, 1963; Publication (Box 79, Folder 41)
    Author: Frederic Freilicher
    Notes: Fall 1963
- Box: 79, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 79, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Experience in Dealing with Job Elimination Resulting from Subcontracting and Other Changes in Methods of Operations, 1966; Publication (Box 79, Folder 42)
    Author: U.S. National Labor Relations Board
- Box: 79, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 79, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: A Subject Matter Classification Plan for Public Personnel Administration, 1964; Publication (Box 79, Folder 43)
    Author: Public Personnel Association
- Box: 79, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 79, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Subsidy and Subsidy-Effect Programs of the U.S. Government, 1965; Publication (Box 79, Folder 44)
- Box: 79, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 79, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Un-American Activities in California, 1963; Publication (Box 79, Folder 45)
    Author: California Senate Factfinding Subcommittee on Un-American Activities
- Box: 79, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 79, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: The Sugar System and the Plantation Workers, Publication (Box 79, Folder 46)
    Author: Robin Myers
- Box: 79, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 79, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Anonymous, Partially, and Fully Identified Suggestion Plans, Publication (Box 79, Folder 47)
    Author: National Association of Suggestion Systems
- Box: 79, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 79, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Employee Suggestion Schemes, Publication (Box 79, Folder 48)
    Author: K.J. Joseph
  - Item 2: Evaluating Intangible Suggestions, Publication (Box 79, Folder 48)
- Box: 79, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 79, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Study of Adoption and Non Adoption Letters, Publication (Box 79, Folder 49)
  - Item 2: Industrial Suggestion Schemes, Publication (Box 79, Folder 49)
    Author: Swedish Council for Personnel Administration
  - Item 3: Objectives of a Suggestion System, Publication (Box 79, Folder 49)
- Box: 79, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 79, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Starting a Suggestion System in Your Organization, Publication (Box 79, Folder 50)
  - Item 2: What Employees Think of Suggestion Plans, Publication (Box 79, Folder 50)
    Author: Robert D. Gray
  - Item 3: Who Needs a Suggestion System?, Publication (Box 79, Folder 50)
  - Item 4: Successful Suggestion Schemes, Publication (Box 79, Folder 50)
  - Item 5: Successful Suggestion Systems, Publication (Box 79, Folder 50)
- Box: 79, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 79, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Successful Supervision Through Better Employee Relations, Publication (Box 79, Folder 51)
    Author: Motivation Inc.
  - Item 2: How to Delegate, Publication (Box 79, Folder 51)
  - Item 3: Fantasies and Facts in Supervision, 1955; Publication (Box 79, Folder 51)
    Author: American Petroleum Institute
    Notes: November 14, 1955
  - Item 4: A Word to Higher Supervision, Publication (Box 79, Folder 51)
  - Item 5: Abc of Supervision, Publication (Box 79, Folder 51)
    Author: University of Illinois
  - Item 6: Unleashing Creativity Through Delegation, Publication (Box 79, Folder 51)
    Author: Julius E. Eitington
  - Item 7: Human Relations in Supervision, Publication (Box 79, Folder 51)
    Author: Teche Area Vocational-Technical School
- Box: 79, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 79, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Course in Management for Supervisors, 1965; Publication (Box 79, Folder 52)
    Author: U.S. General Services Administration
- Box: 80, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Foreman Training Conference, 1937; Publication (Box 80, Folder 1)
    Author: Oregon Board for Vocational Education
    Notes: September 29 - November 17, 1937
- Box: 80, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: W.P.A. Foremanship Training Conferences, 1937; Publication (Box 80, Folder 2)
    Author: Works Progress Administration of Louisiana
    Notes: March 29 - June 24, 1937
- Box: 80, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Job Management Training, Publication (Box 80, Folder 3)
    Author: Air Service Command Supervisor Training
  - Item 2: Problems of Handling Men, Publication (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Box: 80, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Salaried Employees and the Industrial Transformation, 1955; Publication (Box 80, Folder 4)
    Author: Erik Hook
- Box: 80, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Conditions of Payment and of Employment, Publication (Box 80, Folder 5)
    Author: TCO:s Statstjanstemannasektion
- Box: 80, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: For and Against the Welfare State Swedish Experiences, 1963; Publication (Box 80, Folder 6)
    Author: Ernst Michanek
- Box: 80, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Assistant Action of Spanish Syndicalism, 1966; Publication (Box 80, Folder 7)
    Author: Jose Solis Ruiz
- Box: 80, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Declaration of Indignation, Publication (Box 80, Folder 8)
    Author: Foundation for Management Research
- Box: 80, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: An Analysis of the Impact of Taxes on Jobs in New York City, Publication (Box 80, Folder 9)
    Author: New York City Economic Development Council
- Box: 80, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Taxes and the Public Interest, 1963; Publication (Box 80, Folder 10)
    Author: Conference on Economic Progress
  - Item 2: Tax Changes for Shortrun Stabilization, 1966; Publication (Box 80, Folder 10)
    Notes: May 27, 1966
  - Item 3: Tax Burdens and Benefits of Government Expenditures by Income Class, 1967; Publication (Box 80, Folder 10)